ANA KAREN DELGADO PEREZ

613-413-6494

delgado_anakaren@hotmail.com • https://anadelgado96.github.io/ 2969 Fairlea Crescent, Ottawa, Ontario, K1V 9N2

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Front End Developer with over 3 years of experience in structuring, maintaining, and implementing responsive websites. Proficient in HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, React.js, Vue.js, WordPress and Magento. Looking for an opportunity to expand my knowledge in React.js.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Agile Thought LATAM • Mexico City, Mexico

Nov 2019 - Present

- Created multiple landing pages and components of Dolce Gusto's website in Magento.
- Collaborated with a Back End Developer to integrate a React page in Magento that shows the nearest collection points for their Capsule Recycling Program.

Web Developer

May 2018 - Jun 2019

(Internship) UNAM-Canada • Gatineau, Québec

- Created an intranet site using WordPress. This site centralizes important information providing fast and easy access to it and makes collaboration easier.
- Administrated and maintained their WordPress website, managing user permissions and roles and using strategies to improve the SEO.

EDUCATION

Applied Mathematics and Computing, Bachelor

National Autonomous University of Mexico (UNAM) • Mexico

Jul 2014 - May 2018

Graduated Cum Laude

COURSEWORK

Front-End Development with react (Jan 2022)

(The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology - Coursera)

Developed skills in React.js, such as implementing single page applications using various React features
including React components, Reactstrap and React router, creating and validating forms, creating the
architecture for a React-Redux application, using Fetch and the REST API for client-server communication,
testing, building, and deploying React applications.

PROJECTS

Seenapse

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021

Generated the necessary React components for a new feature that allows registered users to get AI
generated ideas, with the use of React forms, and components that render the results of a query to the AI API.